apolloduck.com 2006-11-04

# Boats for sale, used boats, new boat sales, free photo ads - Apollo Duck

[Air Boats](http://www.apolloduck.com/listings.phtml?cid=349) 5  
[Barges](http://barges.apolloduck.com/) 241  
[Boat Builders](http://www.apolloduck.com/listings.phtml?cid=14) 15  
[Boat Charters](http://www.apolloduck.com/listings.phtml?cid=165) 15  
[Boat Shares](http://www.apolloduck.com/listings.phtml?cid=378) 6  
[Boat Trailers](http://www.apolloduck.com/listings.phtml?cid=373) 163  
[Businesses](http://www.apolloduck.com/listings.phtml?cid=379) 5  
[Canoes & Kayaks](http://www.apolloduck.com/listings.phtml?cid=9) 36  
[Chandlery](http://www.apolloduck.com/listings.phtml?cid=12) 88  
[Classic Boats](http://www.apolloduck.com/listings.phtml?cid=352) 48  
[Commercial](http://commercial.apolloduck.com/) 845  
[Day Boats](http://www.apolloduck.com/listings.phtml?cid=356) 42  
[Duck Boats](http://www.apolloduck.com/listings.phtml?cid=85) 1  
[Engines](http://www.apolloduck.com/listings.phtml?cid=10) 459  
[Fishing Boats](http://www.apolloduck.com/listings.phtml?cid=86) 742  
[House Boats](http://www.apolloduck.com/listings.phtml?cid=81) 186  
[Hovercraft](http://www.apolloduck.com/listings.phtml?cid=361) 3  
[Hydrofoils](http://www.apolloduck.com/listings.phtml?cid=371) 1  
[Launches](http://www.apolloduck.com/listings.phtml?cid=36) 23  
[Marinas & Moorings](http://www.apolloduck.com/listings.phtml?cid=16) 195  
[Marine Services](http://www.apolloduck.com/listings.phtml?cid=15) 31  
[Motor Cruisers](http://www.apolloduck.com/listings.phtml?cid=1) 1181  
[Motor Yachts](http://motoryachts.apolloduck.com/) 312  
[Narrow Boats](http://www.apolloduck.com/listings.phtml?cid=140) 424  
[Open Boats](http://www.apolloduck.com/listings.phtml?cid=8) 114  
[PWCs](http://www.apolloduck.com/listings.phtml?cid=11) 49  
[RIBs](http://www.apolloduck.com/listings.phtml?cid=138) 607  
[Rowing](http://www.apolloduck.com/listings.phtml?cid=364) 11  
[Sailing Dinghies](http://www.apolloduck.com/listings.phtml?cid=7) 654  
[Sport Boats](http://www.apolloduck.com/listings.phtml?cid=197) 1259  
[Sport Cruisers](http://www.apolloduck.com/listings.phtml?cid=142) 778  
[Superyachts](http://superyachts.apolloduck.com/) 118  
[Tall Ships](http://www.apolloduck.com/listings.phtml?cid=347) 2  
[Tenders](http://www.apolloduck.com/listings.phtml?cid=6) 154  
[Traditional](http://www.apolloduck.com/listings.phtml?cid=5) 63  
[Waterside Properties](http://www.apolloduck.com/listings.phtml?cid=17) 30  
[Watersports](http://www.apolloduck.com/listings.phtml?cid=13) 16  
[Yachts](http://yachts.apolloduck.com/) 1853  

Privacy Policy  

© 1998-2006  

ALL RIGHTS RESERVED

| 

Apollo Duck Privacy Policy

Santa Monica Airlines takes your privacy seriously. Subject to the terms of the Apollo Duck User Agreement, this statement explains our privacy and data-protection practices. 

It is important for Apollo Duck to safeguard its users' privacy while providing a personalised and valuable service. Collecting some personal information is necessary in order to provide a secure service to uniquely identifiable users. 

  1. What information do we compile?

> In addition to any information given during the advert submission or registration process, information is automatically logged about your browsing behaviour through the site. This log information is only in an aggregate form, and no individual registered user is identified therein. The aggregated data allows us to analyse site traffic and better understand how we can improve the efficiency and value of our services. 

  2. What do we do with the information we collect?

> The limited personal information you supply on your advert submission form or dealer account registration will not be disclosed outwith Santa Monica Airlines. The email address you provide is used as a simple and memorable username for accessing the service. We may use your address to communicate any changes and improvements to the site and service. Each time you receive a message, you have the option to decline to receive further service communications from us. 

  3. What information do our cookies collect?

> Our server issues cookies to every visitor to the Apollo Duck websites. These cookies contain nothing more than a server generated number which is used to distinguish visitors from each other and ensure that your visit is private and separate from all other visitors to the site. These cookies help us to ensure your privacy. No personally identifiable information is recorded by the cookies. 

Copyright © 1998-2006 Santa Monica Airlines Ltd. 

[Silicon Ink  
Property For Sale](http://www.siliconink.com/)

**International  
specialty boat sales:**

**Apollo Duck  
boats for sale  
worldwide:**

International
